mybanktracker.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy for MyBankTracker.com

MyBankTracker, Inc., a New York corporation ("MBT"), owns and operates the Web site located at [www.mybanktracker.com](https://www.mybanktracker.com/), and portions of other Web pages and Web content through which you have accessed this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Web Site"). By visiting, using and/or submitting information to www.mybanktracker.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the terms and conditions of MyBankTracker's Agreement of Terms of (the "Terms of Use").

MBT takes your privacy seriously, and has published this Privacy Policy to explain how MBT treats all information you may submit to the Web Site.

Many of the features of the Web Site are available to you without your providing personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information generally includes information that could be used to determine your identity, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and birth date. The following are certain situations in which MBT may collect personally identifiable information from you: Registration for Newsletters MBT collects personally identifiable information from you if you register online for one of MBT's. When you register online with MBT, MBT asks for personally identifiable information like your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, personal interests and other demographic information. Use of Questions and comments. If you choose to transmit, submit or post information through MBT's chat rooms, bulletin boards or other forums (the "Forums"), MBT will collect that information you provide. MBT retains this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law and pursuant to MBT's Terms of Use. Forms. MBT may collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to fill out any forms, profiles, or surveys on the Web Site. Correspondence. If you send MBT personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send MBT correspondence about your activities or postings on the Web Site, MBT may choose to collect such information into a file specific to you.

MBT uses your personally identifiable information as follows:

  * To improve MBT's marketing and promotional efforts, analyze site usage, improve MBT's content and product offerings, and customize MBT's content, layout, and services;
  * To contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Web Site;
  * To fulfill your requests for certain products and services;
  * For market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity, to enforce MBT's Terms of Use, for other internal purposes, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

You expressly agree to MBT's use of your personally identifiable information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. 

MBT does not currently sell your personally identifiable information. The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business:

Advertisers. MBT may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes. For example, MBT may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose it to network advertisers in a non-personally identifiable manner as set forth in the section entitled "Network Advertisers," set forth below. MBT does not disclose your information in a personally identifiable manner to such third party advertisers without your consent. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, MBT reserves the right (and you authorize MBT) to share or disclose your personally identifiable information when MBT determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of your personally identifiable information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if:

  * You are or may be violating this Privacy Policy or MBT's Terms of Use;
  * You are interfering with another's rights or property, including, without limitation, MBT's rights or property;
  * You are violating any applicable law, rule or regulation;
  * Necessary or required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; and/or
  * Requested by authorities in the event of any act of terrorism or instance of local, regional or national emergency.

Personally identifiable information and other personal information collected from you may also be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization, other transfer or bankruptcy (a "Transfer") involving MBT and/or its affiliates. MBT specifically reserves the right to transfer personally identifiable information collected from the Web Site, and any of its databases, together with any personally identifiable information contained therein, to a third party in connection with a Transfer, and nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of MBT to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets (including the Web Site) to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever.

In addition, due to the existing regulatory environment, MBT cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), MBT may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although MBT uses industry standard practices to protect your privacy, MBT does not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

NOTE: If you are submitting personally identifiable information pursuant to sweepstakes entry, MBT reserves the right to share, loan, rent and/or sell the personally identifiable information that you submit with its affiliates and other third parties. Please refer to the Official Rules and Privacy Policy for each individual sweepstakes for the specific guidelines regarding information sharing and disclosure.

Network Advertising

MBT may use third-party advertising companies for marketing, advertising and promotional purposes, as well as to serve advertisements to you. Using third-party advertising companies helps us and third-party advertisers better determine which advertisements or content to serve to you. For example, the third-party advertisers may use information regarding your visits to the Web Site and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services, that third party advertisers believe will be of interest to you. 

The types of information that may be collected by third-party advertising companies include the following:

  * The type of Internet browser you use; 
  * The type of computer operating system you use;
  * The domain name of a Web site you visit, as well as information related to Web sites and Web pages you are viewing when an advertisement is requested;
  * Whether or not you visit specific pages of the Web Site or other Web sites;
  * The location of your Internet service provider's point of presence;
  * The date and time of a visit to a Web site;
  * Search keywords passed from another server; 
  * The number of times you have clicked on an advertisement; and
  * Other interactions between you and a Web site.

Cookie technology

"Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. MBT, its external service providers, internal service providers, and third-party advertising companies, may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. MBT, and its external service providers, internal service providers, and third-party advertising companies gather anonymous information about you through cookie technology on an aggregate level only. For example, a third-party advertising company may assign a cookie (and a Web beacon, described below) to you, to limit the amount of times you see a particular advertisement or to help better determine which advertisements to serve to you. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer.

Web beacons

"Web beacons", also called single-pixels (1x1) or clear GIFs, are electronic images that allow a Web site to access cookies and help track marketing campaigns and general usage patterns of visitors to those Web sites. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as cookie numbers, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with third parties through the use of Web beacons. 

Security

Personally identifiable information you submit to MBT is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas MBT uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. In the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises MBT security measures, MBT will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party's ability to view, use or disseminate such information.

Links to Other Web sites

the Web Site may include links to other third party Web sites. Such links are not an endorsement by MBT of those Web sites and/or the products or services offered there. Third party Web sites may have different privacy policies and MBT is not responsible for the privacy practices of those third party Web sites. If you click on a link to a third party Web site, MBT encourages you to check the privacy policy of that Web site, as it may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy.

Access and Use of the Web Site

the Web Site is intended to be accessed and used only by adults and is not directed to children under the age of 18. MBT does not knowingly permit registration or submission of personally identifiable information by anyone under the age of 18.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

MBT reserves the right to update, amend and/or change this Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion and without notice.
